Where
do I
begin to tell the story of how great love can be?
The sweet love story that is older than the sea.
The simple truth about the love he brings to me.
What's good, boys?
We just touched down in beautiful Italy.
This is our second, no, third?
No, actually, Finn, how many times have we been in Italy?
The last year?
Four times.
It's our fourth time.
It's our fourth time in Italy the past year.
We are in Italy because we're running an only-air trip.
Just linked up with like half the crew that's coming.
We're going to get some food right now.
Every f***ing time I try to do it, my head just goes up.
As I was saying, we're here for the next four days.
We're running a founder trip, so we've just flown out, well, there's like 10 of us for the trip.
So it should be pretty cool.
Is
it fucking amazing or is it
amazing?
It's fucking amazing.
Amazing.
The crib?
It's not bad.
I stand better.
We're eating pizza.
It's getting carbonated.
Carbonated.
She chose them, so they better be fire.
That's a pretty gas pizza.
But it's pretty small.
I didn't pick the size.
I didn't pick the size of the pizza.
You were sharing.
We're going to be actually raw and realistic right now.
We've been up since 3:30 a.m., and now we're crashing out because it's 10 p.m., and we just got food.
I'm actually not crashing out.
Crashing out because it's also all it's all a perspective thing, right?
Like, I'm so blessed to be here.
We're in Lake Garda.
It's beautiful environment, beautiful people.
Everyone's crushing it.
Life can't be better.
Life can't really be better.
We got pizza.
Boom.
What's
good, Finn?
Boys, day one has officially started.
It's like 7 a.m. right now.
You can see all the boys are coming down.
We're going to go get a coffee.
Going to lock in to do some work.
Happy birthday, boss.
Thank you, bro.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, G. You're getting old, eh?
23s, that's a lot on the sand.
That's when you start pushing.
23 is like, you have to be doing good numbers, otherwise you're trolling.
I think so.
It depends on how long you've been in the game though.
Facts, facts.
If you're just getting started, some people are getting, become billionaires, it's 45, brother.
Yeah, watching this and you thinking about starting, I fucking start.
If you getting old, start cooking.
If you getting old, if you 23, you fucked.
Hurry up and start.
Trying on hats for our boat date tomorrow.
So, what do we say?
Oh, it's a Zizi.
Hey, it's cute.
Is it like go with the outfit?
Wow.
You like it?
Yeah.
She said no!
No!
Let's go, boys!
Now we're gonna go get some groceries, lock in for some work, and we've got tennis.
Just explored this nice town of Gara.
Yeah, we're gonna go get some more food.
How's the birthday boy feeling?
This is easily best birthday out of all 23 of them.
Holy!
That's a big call.
Last year I would have been asleep by probably 9, 9:30 p.m. It's a bit of an upgrade.
So now we've got a black tie event, private chef making a crazy setting, and then we've also got a little surprise after.
We're going to maybe go somewhere a little bit.
Is it?
Oh!
Over the net, buddy.
You're missing because I can't cut to it.
What's happening?
I don't know.
We're just cruising.
We're just playing golf.
I got the golf cart.
I'm gonna go pick up the chef.
We got private dinner.
That's true.
Let's run it.
Can you move the car?
Huh?
Update for the day.
We are just fucking cruising.
Just went and played tennis.
Realized tennis is actually a lot harder than I thought.
Setting up for the black tie dinner.
I thought we'd take this for a little bit of a spin.
Holy smokes, I'm crashing.
So we take this thing for a little bit of a spin and see what it's about.
But it's like he's crazy.
I want to spin it.
We're spinning.
I want to be spinning.
Let's go down again.
I want to be.
I'll spin it up.
Down there.
I'll just spin it.
Wait, let me spin.
Holy, this is such a guys view.
Preparing for the black tie dinner.
We're going to, first of all, enjoy some snacks here.
Have dinner downstairs.
Exactly.
There.
Jasper's birthday.
Jasper's birthday, birthday boy, 23.
It's a big number, big number.
But now we need to get ready.
Let's go.
Boom.
Let's go eat.
Nah, I just wanted to thank everyone for coming.
This is a crazy villa and it's been so fun so far.
Feels like we been here for ages even though it only been like 24 hours.
And I excited for tonight and what to come.
Thank you all for coming.
I, boys take to a mouthy.
Like gotta got the boat today swimming, second last day in Italy tomorrow.
We're gonna go to South France.
I think let's go.
How was how was your birthday yesterday?
I was good.
It was good.
Genuinely like what a day.
You probably can't script a better birthday.
This is full-time cruise.
That's what it feels like to be Noel Trollimo.
Cruise maxing.
Cruise maxing, let's f***ing go.
I need to know what you guys are cooking.
Schnitzels, steaks, vegetables, salad.
We've got some salad going on.
I genuinely don't have a vision yet, but something will happen.
We're gonna cook something yummy.
No more, I just got everything that I could.
And if I only knew where all the stuff in the kitchen was, that would be amazing.
The girl's been cooking.
How you doing?
How you doing, friend?
Got the women of the house cooking us dinner.
The girl's politely offered to make us dinner tonight, which we are very thankful for.
We've got a nice family.
I love Ripple.
We've got some wine.
We've got some potatoes, some avocado, some cold meats, steak, sausages, chicken stinchel.
How's the trip been so far?
I got a bit burnt today, crispy, but am I, am I that burnt or not?
Like just like you're right.
But the trip's been fire.
The trip's been fire.
It's been like the most peaceful place.
We've been getting some stuff done, but it's been good to just like be in a nice like peaceful kind of like country town on the lake.
We went and actually saw everything, and if you're someone that's coming to Italy and you're deciding to go to Lake Como or wherever, I recommend just go
to Lake Garda.
It likely more fire than Lake Como.
Probably a bit easier if you fly into Venice.
So we done it again.
We done it again.
We fucking done it again.
You can like very clearly see from all the vlogs every trip just gets better and better, better.
So Miami's gonna be fucking crazy, and yeah, right now just gonna enjoy a nice final dinner, and then half the group leaves tomorrow.
The other half are gonna actually just come and travel with us because we're all in Europe, so we may as well just go travel together.
So yeah, we're gonna have half the people coming with us, half people have to go home, got business to do.
And then yeah, we'll take you guys along as my next vlog coming out will be South France and Monaco, which will be pretty lady.
My name is Laurent.
My first trip out here with Only Earned.
Laurent.
They don't know how to pronounce it.
It's Yves Saint Laurent.
It's a French appellation.
But yeah, I run an agency, website agency, but not so long ago started coaching others how to do the same thing.
I'm currently ripping some good months but trying to scale it up to six figure months, and that's why I'm with the squad.
I've done Amalfi, I've done nice places, but I can say confidently Lake Garda.
Especially like Finn said, Lake Garda over Lake Como.
Guys, look at this.
I mean, can't beat this view, can't beat this place as well.
So, amazing trip.
What happened today?
Did you have some business today?
Yo, I closed one and potentially two more as well.
The works, but talking business with a bunch of people as well, and uh, opening opportunities, real bro, that's that's what it's about, that's why I
joined, or couldn't be more grateful.
His view does not get old, and it's been really cool meeting new people, um, all very dialed in in business
as just said, but no, it's been awesome.
Finn and Noel have absolutely smashed it out of the park again.
I'm not surprised.
We're gonna France, we're going to Monaco, we're going to Monaco, baby, yes, France, it's gonna be sick.
Cooking, okay, so we made potatoes, then
we have a sweet potato.
And carrots with honey, actually.
So let's try.
Then we have salad with feta and apple and tomatoes and rucola, so we have a cool summer salad with a bit of pizza.
Now I'm nervous.
Then we have here schnitzel à la Nicolina's recipe.
Then we have potatoes, oven potatoes, and then we have avocado.
It's gonna be a very good dinner.
Yes.
Love was just a glance away, a warm embracing dance away.